<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.1.2//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.0/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY todolist "<application><emphasis>Todolist.php</emphasis></application>">
]>
<book lang="en">
<?dbhtml filename="todolist.html"?>
<title>Manual for Todolist.php</title>
<bookinfo>
<author>
  <firstname>Jörg</firstname>
  <surname>Menke</surname>
  <affiliation>
    <address><email>jhm@gmx.net</email></address>
  </affiliation>
</author>
<copyright>
  <year>1999</year>
  <year>2000</year>
  <year>2001</year>
  <holder>Jörg Menke</holder>
</copyright>
<legalnotice>
  <para>This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU
    General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License,
    or (at your option) any later version.</para>

  <para>This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without
    even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General
    Public License for more details.</para>

  <para>You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; if not,
    write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc., 675 Mass Ave, Cambridge, MA 02139, USA.</para>
</legalnotice>
<abstract>
  <para>
    &todolist; is a set of PHP scripts that create a web-based list of things to do.
  </para>
</abstract>
<date>07.10.2001</date>
</bookinfo>


<preface>
  <title>Preface</title>
  <para>
    &todolist; is a set of PHP scripts that create a web-based list of things to do.  Items can be added and
    removed, and are sorted by an assigned priority.  Also it is possible to assign special tasks to another
    person and for example to specify a due date. ToDoList is multilingual (although some languages are still
    under development). Lots of unmentioned features.
  </para>
  <para>
    &todolist; was inspired by "todo", some CGI-Scripts, written by Marc Bayerkohler and Joel Thomas. It was
    started because I wanted to learn PHP3 and really needed an easy to use todo-list for the IT-Service-Dep.
    I worked at.  Max joined in April 2001 and brought a more extensible rewrite of much of it with him.
  </para>
  <para>
    This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
    Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at your
    option) any later version.  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT
    ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
    See the GNU General Public License <ulink url="http://www.opensource.org/licenses/gpl-license.html" /> for
    more details.
  </para>
  <para>
    If you have any suggestions or wishes for future versions feel free to contact me and subscribe to the
    mailing-list.
  </para>

  <para>
    Have fun, Jörg Menke <ulink url="mailto:jhm@gmx.net"/>
  </para>
</preface>


<chapter>
  <title>Getting started</title>
  <sect1>
    <title>Requirements</title>
    <para>
      All you need is an PHP-enabled web-server (Apache preferred) and mySQL. It is developed
      with a mod_php-Version of PHP and Apache under Linux. When you use the CGI-Version of
      PHP you'll have some (smaller) limitations, p.e.  remembering the last person that
      logged in doesn't work at the moment. Other databases will (maybe) be supported in the
      future.
    </para>
  </sect1>
</chapter>


<chapter>
  <title>Working with &todolist;</title>
  <para> ... </para>
</chapter>


<chapter>
  <title>Administration of &todolist;</title>
  <sect1 id="project-admin">
    <title>Project-Administration</title>
    <para>
      ...
    </para>
  </sect1>
  <sect1 id="user-admin">
    <title>User-Administration</title>
    <para>
      ...
    </para>
  </sect1>
  <sect1 id="group-admin">
    <title>Group-Administration</title>
    <para>
      Group-support is not yet implemented. Sorry.
    </para>
  </sect1>
</chapter>

<appendix>
  <title>Installation</title>
  <para>
    The installation of the program is very easy. Only a few steps are needed:
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
	<para>the .php files somewhere where they are accessible by the webserver</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  create the database-tables (just run the "databasestructure.sql" in mysql)
	  <programlisting>$ mysql -u DBUSER DBINSTANCE < databasestructure.sql</programlisting>
	</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  Login as the admin user, and set up whatever users you need. A "test"-user with
	  password "test" is also created as example by the setup sql script.
	</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  with the admin-user you can also create projects and assign members to them.  Every
	  newly created user is automatically member of project '1' which is named - guess it -
	  'default'. The default-project shouldn't be deleted.
	</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>edit the "include/config.inc"-file to fit your needs.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  Change the password for user "admin"! (Default password is "admin"....)
	</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </para>
</appendix>
</book>
<!-- vim: set sw=2 tw=110: -->
